Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series V. Press Office: Photographs (Accession 39658 and 40171), 1998-2001 circa.., Extent: 28.5 cu. ft. (Box 101-130)
  - A. Photographs, negatives and contact sheets, 1998-2000.
    - Mental Health announcement, Conference Room (Event #98440), 1998 December 16 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - EPU holiday reception, Executive Mansion (Event #98441), 1998 December 16 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Annual Gilmore holiday party, Executive Mansion (Event #98442), 1998 December 18 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Open House, Executive Mansion (Event #98443), 1998 December 19 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Black tie dinner with VIP guests, Executive Mansion (Event #98444), 1998 December 19 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Holiday reception, Executive Mansion (Event #98445), 1998 December 21 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Index to January photographs, 1999 January (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Henrico Business Council, Richmond Hyatt (Event #99446), 1999 January 6 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Education press conference re: school report cards, Conference Room (Event #99447), 1999 January 6 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Interior and exterior photographs for The Web of Time magazine, Executive Mansion (Event #99448), 1999 January 7 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Congressional delegation meeting (Event #99449), 1999 January 11 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Congressional delegation group photograph (Event #99450), 1999 January 11 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - State of the Commonwealth address, House Chamber (Event #99451), 1999 January 13 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Ribbon cutting at Sussex II Maximum Security Prison, Sussex, VA (Event #99452), 1999 January 18 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Press conference with Inspector General Dr. Anita Everett, Conference Room (Event #99453), 1999 January 19 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Miss America Organization with Miss America Nicole Johnson, Conference Room (Event #99454), 1999 January 19 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Teen Pack, Capitol Grounds (Event #99455), 1999 January 22 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Live closed circuit Y2K program, DIT (Event #99456), 1999 January 22 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Mark Herndon, Executive Mansion (Event #99457), 1999 January 25 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Fraternal Order of Police, VDOT Auditorium (Event #99458), 1999 January 27 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Interior photographs of the Executive Mansion, 2nd floor (Event #99459), 1999 January 27 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Energy Recovery Systems, Sustainable Energy Industrial Park, Cape Charles, VA (Event #99460), 1999 January 29 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Index to February photographs, 1999 February (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Press conference - Top Fiscal Management announcement (Event #99461), 1999 February 1 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Town officials from Dumfries, VA, Conference Room (Event #99462), 1999 February 1 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Terrorism Conference (FEMA, A.G. Janet Reno, NC Governor Hunt), Williamsburg Lodge (Event #99463), 1999 February 2 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - Terrorism Conference press conference, Williamsburg Lodge (Event #99464), 1999 February 2 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - Portrait sitting for Cathan Currin III, Governor's Employment and Training Dept., Old Library Building (Event #99465), 1999 February 3 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - Eternal Tech (Taiwan) announcement, House Room 5 (Event #99466), 1999 February 4 (Box 110, Folder 30)
    - Lt. Governor Hager with Lee County Officials, Lt. Governor's Office (Event #99467), 1999 February 5 (Box 110, Folder 31)
    - Gateway announcement, Hampton, VA (Event #99468), 1999 February 5 (Box 110, Folder 32)
    - Black tie dinner, Executive Mansion (Event #99469), 1999 February 5 (Box 110, Folder 33)
    - Expansion announcement, Capital One, Richmond, VA (Event #99470), 1999 February 9 (Box 110, Folder 34)
    - CIT Board, Library of Virginia (Event #99471), 1999 February 10 (Box 110, Folder 35)
    - Senator Randy Forbes with school groups, Library of Virginia (Event #99471), 1999 February 10 (Box 110, Folder 36)
    - Press conference for Mark Early (Event #99473), 1999 February 10 (Box 110, Folder 37)
    - Press conference on illegal medical waste, House Room 5 (Event #99474), 1999 February 11 (Box 110, Folder 38)
    - Mental Health awards, The Jefferson Hotel, Richmond, VA (Event #99475), 1999 February 11 (Box 110, Folder 39)
    - Departure photograph for Christian Ferry, Executive Mansion (Event #99476), 1999 February 12 (Box 110, Folder 40)
    - Virginia Tobacco Growers Conference, South Boston, VA (Event #99477), 1999 February 13 (Box 110, Folder 41)
    - Anniversary celebration at Mount Vernon, Alexandria, VA (Event #99478), 1999 February 15 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Reception at Mount Vernon, Alexandria, VA (Event #99479), 1999 February 15 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - YMCA Youth Governor, Conference Room (Event #99480), 1999 February 15 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Terry Kilgore with school group from Gate City, Conference Room (Event #99481), 1999 February 15 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Reception for House and Senate pages, Executive Mansion (Event #99482), 1999 February 15 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Legislative reception, Executive Mansion (Event #99483), 1999 February 10 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Portrait sitting for Mark Miner, Conference Room (Event #99484), 1999 February 11 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Senator Potts and Coach Thompson (Georgetown basketball), Governor's private office (Event #99485), 1999 February 16 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - SCHEV awards, Old Senate Chamber (Event #99486), 1999 February 17 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Black History Month reception, Executive Mansion (Event #99487), 1999 February 18 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Portrait sitting for Susan Dewey, State Treasurer, Old Library Building (Event #99488), 1999 February 23 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Delegate Kilgore and Senator Wampler iwth Gate City officials, Conference Room (Event #99489), 1999 February 24 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Index to March photographs, 1999 March (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Theme Park vacation announcement, South Portico (Event #99490), 1999 March 5 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Aircraft Carrier Tech Center, Newport News, VA (Event #99491), 1999 March 9 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - AOL at Battlefield Industrial Park, Prince William County, VA (Event #99492), 1999 March 10 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Alpha, Beta, Boule, Henderson Student Center, Virginia Union University (Event #99493), 1999 March 12 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - EPU, ID photographs, Executive Mansion (Event #99494), 1999 March 13 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Governor and Delegate Eric Cantor, Conference Room (Event #99495), 1999 March 15 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Elizabeth Dole, Governor's private office (Event #99496), 1999 March 18 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Mort Kunstler dinner, Executive Mansion (Event #99497), 1999 March 18 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Economic Development announcement re: Innotech / Johnson and Johnson, Roanoke, VA (Event #99498), 1999 March 19 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Roanoke City Economic Development meeting, Hotel Roanoke (Event #99499), 1999 March 19 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Interior photographs of the Executive Mansion, 1st Floor (Event #99500), 1999 March 23 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Portrait sitting for Lonnie Craig, Capitol Police Superintendent, Old Library Building (Event #99501), 1999 March 24 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Portrait sitting for Dr. Anita S. Everett, Inspector General, Old Library Building (Event #99502), 1999 March 24 (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Portrait sitting for Brenda F. Haley, Health and Human Resources, Old Library Building (Event #99503), 1999 March 24 (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Portrait sitting for James Laws, Dept. of Education, Old Library Building (Event #99504), 1999 March 25 (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - Portrait sitting for Ruby Rogers, Dept. of Education, Old Library Building (Event #99505), 1999 March 25 (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - Portrait sitting for Audrey B. Davis, Dept. of Education, Old Library Building (Event #99506), 1999 March 25 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Portrait sitting for Susan Noble, Dept. of Education, Old Library Building (Event #99507), 1999 March 25 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Information Technologies bill signing, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, DC (Event #99508), 1999 March 30 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Electronic Industry Alliance award luncheon, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, DC (Event #99509), 1999 March 30 (Box 111, Folder 33)
    - Portrait sitting for Michael McSherry, ID photograph (Event #99510), 1999 March 30 (Box 111, Folder 34)
    - Walk through new Governor's residence with DGS (Event #99511), 1999 April 1 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Liaison Office personnel, Virginia Liaison Office, Washington, DC (Event #99512), 1999 April 5 (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - Vance Wilkins - House Bill 2023, Conference Room (Event #99513), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 37)
    - Steve Landis - House Bill 1593 and Senate Bill 1027, Conference Room (Event #99514), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 38)
    - Terry Kilgore - House Bill 1688, Conference Room (Event #99515), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - Russell Potts - Senate Bill 830, Conference Room (Event #99516), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 40)
    - Dave Albo - House Bill 1468, Conference Room (Event #99517), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 41)
    - Executive Mansion interiors - moving process (Event #99518), 1999 April 7 (Box 111, Folder 42)
    - Swearing in of Mansion Committee members, Executive Mansion (Event #99519), 1999 April 8 (Box 111, Folder 43)
    - Ribbon cutting ceremony at Wallen's Ridge Prison, Big Stone Gap, VA (Event #99520), 1999 April 9 (Box 111, Folder 44)
    - Concrete industry trade group, Roanoke, VA (Event #99521), 1999 April 13 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - YMCA Model General Assembly, St. Paul's Church, Richmond, VA (Event #99522), 1999 April 16 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - George Bush announcement, House Room 5 (Event #99523), 1999 April 16 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Moving process continued, Executive Mansion (Event #99524), 1999 April 16 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Moving process continued, Executive Mansion (Event #99525), 1999 April 19 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Hampton Roads Marine Association, Norfolk, VA (Event #99526), 1999 April 22 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Residence level moving process (morning), Executive Mansion (Event #99527), 1999 April 23 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Residence level moving process (afternoon), Executive Mansion (Event #99528), 1999 April 23 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - VMIL review and address, Mary Baldwin College, Staunton, VA (Event #99529), 1999 April 26 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Address to Larry Sabato's class, Wilson Hall Auditorium, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Event #99530), 1999 April 26 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Address to Larry Sabato's class - speaking to students, Wilson Hall Auditorium, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Event #99531), 1999 April 26 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Portrait sitting for Mike Taylor of EPU, Old Library Building (Event #99532), 1999 April 27 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Portrait sitting for Dennis Treacy of DEQ, Old Library Building (Event #99533), 1999 April 27 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Portrait sitting for Ron Hamm of DEQ, Old Library Building (Event #99534), 1999 April 27 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Passport photographs for Ryan Frasier and Gail Vermillen, Capitol (Event #99535), 1999 April 29 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - ASPCA Hair Ball, The Jefferson Hotel, Richmond, VA (Event #99536), 1999 April 29 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Ashton's band concert, St. Christopher's School, Richmond, VA (Event #99537), 1999 April 29 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - SCHEV - College Board of Visitors, Omni Hotel, Richmond, VA (Event #99538), 1999 April 30 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Visit to Constituent Services, 9th Street Office Building (Event #99539), 1999 May 3 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Announcement of Henrico judgeships (Catherine Hammond and Gary Hicks), House Room 5 (Event #99540), 1999 May 4 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - School safety announcement with Attorney General Mark Early, South Portico (Event #99541), 1999 May 10 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Lord Hanningfield, Conference Room (Event #99542), 1999 May 14 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) graduation, Richmond Coliseum (Event #99543), 1999 May 15 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Virginia State University (VSU) graduation, VSU Campus (Event #99544), 1999 May 16 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Business Appreciation Week breakfast, Richmond Marriott (Event #99545), 1999 May 17 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - United Airlines terminal, Rio de Janiero, Brazil (Event #99546), 1999 May 23 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Sugarloaf Mountain, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99547), 1999 May 23 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Christ the Redeemer, Corcovado Mountain, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99548), 1999 May 23 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Virginia delegation reception, Copacabana Hotel, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99549), 1999 May 23 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - U. S. Consulate briefing, Vermelho Salon, Copacabana Palace, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99550), 1999 May 24 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Governor's address to the American Chamber of Commerce, The American Club, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99551), 1999 May 24 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Announcement with Pittston Coal, Vermelho Salon, Copacabana Palace, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99552), 1999 May 24 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Governor's and Consul General's reception, Consul General's residence, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #995), 1999 May 24 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Announcement with VTLS, Inc., State University of Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99554), 1999 May 25 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Brazilian Port luncheon, The Lynx by Angela, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil (Event #99555), 1999 May 25 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - VIP Lounge, Sau Paulo Airport, Brazil (Event #99556), 1999 May 25 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Governor's address and luncheon, 1431 Rua La Paz, American Chamber, Brazil (Event #99557), 1999 May 26 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - AV program, tour and contract signing, Envipco, Brazil (Event #99558), 1999 May 26 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Governor's and Consulate's reception, Consul General's residence, Brazil (Event #99559), 1999 May 26 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Governor and Secretary Ybarra visit with Metalurgica Mogi Guacu, Mogi Guacu, Brazil (Event #99560), 1999 May 27 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Governor and Secretary Ybarra at Port luncheon, Churrascaria Reo dos Pampas, Limeira, Brazil (Event #99561), 1999 May 27 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Governor and Secretary Ybarra on sales call to Meritor de Brazil, Steel wheel manufacturing plant, Limeira, Brazil (Event #99562), 1999 May 27 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Governor Gilmore with Governor of Santa Catarina, Florianopolis, Santa Catarina, Brazil (Event #99563), 1999 May 28 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Executive affirmation of Sister State relationship, Florianopolis, Santa Catarina, Brazil (Event #99564), 1999 May 28 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Luncheon and Host Committee, Florianopolis, Santa Catarina, Brazil (Event #99565), 1999 May 28 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Island tour, Florianopolis, Santa Catarina, Brazil (Event #99566), 1999 May 28 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Reception, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99567), 1999 May 29 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Governor, Secretary Duval and hosts, Prince of Wales Country Club, Santiago, Chile (Event #99568), 1999 May 30 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Shopping in 400 year old village, Centrin Artestal Los Dominicos, Santiago, Chile (Event #99569), 1999 May 40 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Delegation reception, Governor's Suite, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99570), 1999 May 30 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Breakfast meeting, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99571), 1999 May 30 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Meeting with business leaders, Santiago Chamber of Commerce, Chile (Event #99572), 1999 May 31 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Meeting with VFP (Bell South), Governor's Suite, Sheraton, Sanitago, Chile (Event #99573), 1999 May 31 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Meeting with Rehrig (shop carts), Governor's Suite, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99574), 1999 May 31 (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - Reception hosted by the Governor and Ambassador John O'Leary, Santiago, Chile (Event #99575), 1999 May 31 (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - Price Waterhouse Cooper breakfast, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99576), 1999 June 1 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Chile and Latin America Gener Corporation, Sheraton, Santiago, Chile (Event #99577), 1999 June 1 (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon with Chilean port officials, Aqui Esta Coco Restaurant, Santiago, Chile (Event #99578), 1999 June 1 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Breakfast meeting, Marriott Plaza Hotel, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99579), 1999 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Bus tour of Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99580), 1999 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Comdex/Infocom, Predio Ferial de Palermo, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99581), 1999 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Lunch with FastComm, Rio Alba Restaurant, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99582), 1999 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Dominion Resources reception (Event #99583), 1999 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Port meeting with Maersk Lines, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99584), 1999 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Luncheon with Montemar and Austral, Intercontinental Hotel, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99585), 1999 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Dinner Theater, Senor Tango, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99586), 1999 June 3 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Meeting and luncheon with Dupont, The American Club of Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99587), 1999 June 4 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Governor and Secretay Duval in meeting with Argentine Secretary of Communications, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Event #99588), 1999 June 4 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - 250th Anniversary Celebration, Culpeper, VA (Event #99589), 1999 May 17 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Asian reception, Library of Virginia (Event #99590), 1999 May 1812 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Commonwealth Transportation Board, VDOT Building (Event #99591), 1999 May 19 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Index to June photographs, 1999 June (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Swearing of Judge Catherine Hammond, Henrico Circuit Court (Event #99592), 1999 June 10 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - U. S. Mint - Virginia quarter, Conference Room (Event #99593), 1999 June 11 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - U. S. Small Business luncheon, Richmond Marriott (Event #99594), 1999 June (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Sieman's Information and Communications Network, Reston, VA (Event #99595), 1999 June 15 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Portrait sitting for Martin K. Johnson and J. William Reid - Administration, Finance Building (Event #99596), 1999 June 16 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Portrait sitting for Mary Morris - State Treasurer, Finance Building (Event #99597), 1999 June 17 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Governor's Fellows, Conference Room (Event #99598), 1999 June 28 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Governor's remarks to the Transportation Committee, General Assembly Building (Event #99599), 1999 June 29 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Portrait sitting for John Mahone (Event #99600), 1999 June 29 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Pharming Healthcare, Conference Room (Event #99601), 1999 June 29 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Index to July photographs, 1999 July (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Volvo expansion, Dublin, VA (Event #99602), 1999 July 1 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Institute of Forensic Science and Medicine, Virginia Bio Tech Park (Event #99603), 1999 July 2 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Virginia School Board Association, Richmond Marriott (Event #99604), 1999 July 20 (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - Portrait sitting for Martika A. Parson - Attorney General's Office, Finance Building (Event #99605), 1999 July 21 (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Governor's Fellows picnic, Executive Mansion (Event #99606), 1999 July 27 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - Kraft Foods announcement, Winchester, VA (Event #99607), 1999 July 29 (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - Index to August photographs, 1999 August (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Portrait sitting for Bill Leighty, VRS Headquarters (Event #99608), 1999 August 4 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Teacher's Institute dinner, Executive Mansion (Event #99609), 1999 August 4 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Commonwealth's Attorney's dinner (Event #99610), 1999 August 6 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Portrait sitting for Phyllis Palmeiro - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99611), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Portrait sitting for Karl L. Schilling - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99612), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Portrait sitting for Belinda Anderson - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99613), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Portrait sitting for Dan Hix - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99614), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Portrait sitting for Fran Bradford - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99615), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Portrait sitting for G. Paul Nardo - SCHEV, Finance Building (Event #99616), 1999 August 24 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Assorted images of Mrs. Gilmore visiting schools in Brazil [negatives only] (Event #99617), 1999 August 27 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Copy work from Executive Mansion original images (Event #99618), 1999 August 27 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Portrait sitting for Adele Johnson - VSU, Finance Building (Event #99619), 1999 August 27 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Various photo ops, Governor's conference room (Event #99620), 1999 August (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Transportation Policy press conference, Key Bridge Marriott, Rosslyn, VA (Event #99621), 1999 August 31 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Index to September photographs, 1999 September (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Portrait sitting for Dawn Hively - Liaison Office, Executive Mansion (Event #99622), 1999 September 1 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - David Anderson reception, Temporary Executive Mansion (Event #99623), 1999 September 9 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Press conference for SABRE and Drug Kingpin announcement, Capitol South Portico (Event #99624), 1999 September 20 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Right Choices for Youth reception, Executive Mansion (Event #99625), 1999 September 22 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Right Choices for Youth morning session, VCU Siegel Center (Event #99626), 1999 September 23 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Right Choices for Youth afternoon session, VCU Siegel Center (Event #99627), 1999 September 23 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Environmental Awards, Old Senate Chamber (Event #99628), 1999 September 29 (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Index to October photographs, 1999 October (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Emergency relief announcement, Franklin, VA (Event #99629), 1999 October 1 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Tour of flooded downtown area of Franklin, VA (Event #99630), 1999 October 1 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Executive Mansion dining table, Old Library Building (Event #99631), 1999 October 6 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Technology Outreach Program, VCU Student Commons (Event #99649), 1999 November 9 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Judge James R. Spencer and son, Conference Room (Event #99650), 1999 November 12 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Ambassador and Consulate General with Secretary Duval (Event #99651), 1999 November 16 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Portrait sitting for EPU Trooper Michael McKinney, Conference Room (Event #99652), 1999 November 12 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Henrico School Achievement Awards ceremony, Jefferson Hotel, Richmond (Event #99653), 1999 November 22 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Project Exile road sign, I-95 South - 2 miles south of the Wilson Bridge (Event #), 1999 November 23 (Box 116, Folder 6)